Communications Workers of America (CWA), Local 1104, Education Division; Records apap132
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Photos and Memorabilia, 2000; Undated; 7; 0.6 cubic ft.
  - CWA: Taking a Stand for Justice Poster, Undated (Flat-file 1)
  - GSEU/CWA Affiliation Referendum Poster, Undated (Flat-file 1)
  - Justice for GSEU (Featuring names of petition signers) Poster, Undated (Flat-file 1)
  - We Are the GSEU (Featuring names of members statewide) Poster, Undated (Flat-file 1)
  - Tomb of the Unknown Graduate Student....Poster, Undated (Flat-file 2)
  - Laid to Rest While we Wait for a Contract....Poster, Undated (Flat-file 2)
  - Keep Convention Annual (2) Poster, Undated (Flat-file 2)
  - SUNY Works Because We Do! and Contract Now! (Double-sided) Poster, Undated (Flat-file 2)
- Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improper Practice Charges, Surveys([RESTRICTED]), 1983-1999; Undated; 8; 3.0 cubic ft.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  Arranged alphabetically by type.
  This series contains an array of documents that represent individual member information of a sensitive nature. The applications, grievances, and surveys are from all four SUNY center schools.
  - Affidavit: Theresa Eddins, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 1)
  - Bargaining Survey, Buffalo, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 2)
  - CWA Agency Fee Report: State University of New York, 1994 November 03-1994 December 09 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 3-5)
  - CWA Member Report: State University of NY, 1995 March 21-1995 March 30 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 6-8)
  - CWA Member Report: State University of NY, 1995 September 13 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 9)
  - CWA Member Report: State University of NY, 1995 October 10 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 10)
  - CWA Member Report: State University of NY, 1998 July 28 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 11)
  - Depositions: Lack of Supervision, English & Psychology, Buffalo, 1984; 1986 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 12)
  - Grievance: Address and Phones of Other GA/TA Unions, Stony Brook, 1995 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 13)
  - Grievance: Architecture Department, Buffalo, 1994-1996 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 14)
  - Grievance: Architecture Department, Buffalo, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 15)
  - Grievance: Chemistry GSEU, Buffalo, 1994 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 16)
  - Grievance: College of Arts and Sciences, Buffalo, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 17)
  - Grievance: Comp Fee, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 18)
  - Grievance: Comparative Literature, Buffalo, 1995 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 19)
  - Grievance: Contract Violation, English Dept., Buffalo, 1995 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 20)
  - Grievance: Domestic Partner Rights, Buffalo, 1995 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 21)
  - Grievance: English Department, Buffalo, 1993-1997 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 22)
  - Grievance: HI/ECE, 1996 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 23)
  - Grievance: Humanities T.A. Stony Brook, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 24)
  - Grievance: Initial Contact Form, Applied Math Dept., Stony Brook, 1995 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 25)
  - Grievance: In-State Tuition, Buffalo, 1995 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 26)
  - Grievance: Learning Center, Buffalo, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 27)
  - Grievance: Math TA Line, Buffalo, 1995 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 28)
  - Grievance: Millard Fillmore College, Buffalo, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 29)
  - Grievance: Modern Languages, Buffalo, 1997 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 30)
  - Grievance: Notice of Employment Changes- Binghamton, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 31)
  - Grievance: Panel, Buffalo, 1994-1996 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 32)
  - Grievance: PERB  Jerry George, Buffalo, 1999 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 33)
  - Grievance: Peter Murphy, Buffalo, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 34)
  - Grievance: Pietras  Biography, Buffalo, 1997 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 35)
  - Grievance: Presidential, Buffalo, 1998 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 36)
  - Grievance: Psychology, Buffalo, 1987 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 37)
  - Grievance: Research Institute on Alcoholism  Alcohol Abuse, Buffalo and Albany, 1984 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 38)
  - Grievance: Retroactive Pay Raise, Buffalo, 1994 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 39)
  - Grievance: Right to Stipend, Buffalo, 1995 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 40)
  - Grievance: Staff Association, Buffalo, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 41)
  - GSEU/CWA - Bargaining Survey, 1992 (Box 1 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 42-43)
  - GSEU/CWA - Bargaining Survey, 1992 (Box 2 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 1)
  - GSEU Bargaining Survey, 1995 Spring (Box 2 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 2-13)
  - GSEU/CWA Membership Applications - Albany, 1986 (Box 2 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 14)
  - GSEU/CWA Membership Applications - Albany, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 15)
  - GSEU/CWA Membership Applications - Albany, 1999 (Box 2 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 16)
  - GSEU/CWA Membership Applications - Albany, 1984 (Box 2 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 17)
  - GSEU/CWA Membership Applications - Albany, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 18)
  - GSEU/CWA Membership Applications - Albany, 1991-1994 (Box 2 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 19)
  - GSEU/CWA Membership Applications  Buffalo, 1991-1994 (Box 3 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 1)
  - Jerry Georges PERB Case, 1999 (Box 3 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 2-5)
  - Improper Practice Charge - Reduced Tuition Waiver, Albany, 1996 (Box 3 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 6)
  - Membership Drive Cards, 1982-1983 (Box 3 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 7-9)
  - Membership Drive Cards, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 10)
  - Membership Drive Cards-RAs, 1983 (Box 3 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 11)
  - Staff Appraisals, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 3 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 12)
  - Survey Data Analysis Output, 1994 December (Box 3 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 13)
  - Unit Clarification Questionnaire, 1995 (Box 3 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 14)
  - Weekly Commitment Sheets, 1990-1991 (Box 3 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 15-16)
  - Weekly Commitment Sheets, 1992 February-September (Box 3 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 17)
  - Weekly Commitment Sheets, 1992 September (Box 3 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 18)
  - Weekly Commitment Sheets, 1992 October (Box 3 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 19-20)
  - Weekly Commitment Sheets, 1992 November-1992 December (Box 3 (8-Membership Papers: Applications, Grievances/Improp), Folder 21)